Ceel Wang

User interface designer with 2 years of experience of web development, responsive web design and human-centered design process. Designed with multiple target audiences and complete development process from user research to final product mockups. Provide strong aesthetic visual skill based on usability and readability with steady research and testing. A fast learner, creative problem solver and passionate with current technology and design trend.

Skill

Adobe series, Sketch, Zeplin, HTML, CSS

Language

Mandarin, Native

English, Fluent,

GEPT High-intermediate level, TOEIC 940/990.

Education

National Taiwan University (2010-2014)

Library and Information Science Bachelor of Arts

Creativity and Entrepreneurship Program Art and Design Program

Experience

YOTTA online course, UIUX Designer

2015.12-2017.3

- --The core member of the start-up, originally graphic designer then self-taught into UI fields. Capable of design process, tools and communication skill between different department.
- --Worked independently but cooperated with project manager and development team.
- --Redesigned the information structure and applied responsive web design to the platform.
- --Experienced designing different interface for multiple target audiences, members and teachers.
- --Boosted the valid member account from 2000 to 13000.

MOsi Technologies, LLC, UIUX Designer

2014.1-2014.4

- --Designed the application interface for manufacturing data collection dashboards.
- --Worked closely with developers.

Project

Shanchi(享吃) FoodSharing App

2017.9-

- --A side project aims for better information delivering of food sharing, intending to decrease food waste from individual aspect.
- --Researching food waste information and user needs, generating user journey map, user story, functional map, flow charts, wireframes, and UI mockups for the location-based app.
- --Held a food sharing activity to get face to face with users.
- --Leading the group discussion.

Human Centered design online course

2016.6-2016.10

- --Worked on solving the problem of one-time use utensils causing environmental pollution issue.
- --Executed with design thinking process from qualitative survey, field survey, personas, to brainstorming more than a hundred of solutions.

Design Thinking workshop facilitator

2012.9-

- --Facilitated a two-day workshop as coach and lecturer.
- --Familiar with design thinking process and coaching skills.
- --Participated in NTU, NTUxStanford, Dong Hua University workshops, etc.





- 兩年 UIUX 設計經驗,能獨立作業
- 了解前端框架能夠與工程師溝通
- 換位思考、關注社會議題
- 個性幽默好相處

技術

Adobe series, Sketch, Zeplin, HTML, CSS

語言

中文 母語 英文 流利

- 全民英檢中高級
- 多益 940 分。

學歷

國立台灣大學

圖書資訊學系 (2010-2014)

創意創業學程 藝術設計學程

- 熟悉響應式網站設計 (RWD)、電子商務
- 了解使用者中心設計、設計思考、數位產品開發流程
- 利用閒暇時間參加數個相關讀書會、專案精進領域知識
- 關注產業最新發展,多從歐美吸收最新知識

經驗

YOTTA 線上教育平台, UIUX 設計師

2015.12-2017.3

- 公司草創成員,從平面設計轉做 UI,透過自學、上課與參加社群聚會學會所需技能,包括 UX/UI 流程、軟體操作、與工程師溝通之前端基礎。 - 能夠獨立完成產品介面設計,同時具備與 PM 和 RD 溝通設計和工程需
- 能夠獨立完成產品介面設計,同時具備與 PM 和 RD 溝通設計和工程需求的能力。
- 重新為電子螢幕設計兼具現代感及識別度的企業識別,構造簡單清楚但同時具備高變化度,可以配合不同載體和行銷規劃呈現不同風貌。
- 網站改版, 重新規劃網頁 UI flow 及製作 hi-fi prototype, 並加入 RWD 設計以符合現代網頁使用流程。
- 設計網站兩種不同使用者「學員」及「講師」之操作介面,改善前、後台操作流程及一致性。
- 改版後會員人數從 2000 人上升至 13000 多人,並持續上升中。

MOSi 曜陽整合科技有限公司, UIUX 設計師

2014.1-2014.4

- 設計工廠生產數據管理後台介面,軟體識別和相關平面宣傳圖。
- 據功能架構生產介面設計,與工程師和產品經理討論與改善元素設計和版面配置。.

車案

享吃 - 食物共享 APP

2017.9-

- 自發專案,設計一款讓食物分享資訊流通更即時、方便的 APP,希望 透過加速分享食物過程減少消費者端的食物浪費。
- 從消費者端食物浪費議題著手,進行議題研究、使用者訪談分析、旅程 地圖、競品分析、再進入產品設計過程。

Human Centered design 線上課程

2016.6-2016.10

- 參加 IDEO.org 開的設計思考線上課,題目為解決台灣外食使用一次性 餐具造成的環境污染,從搜集資訊、田野調查到定義問題,最後產生百 個解決方案。

設計思考工作坊教練

2012.9-

- 熟知設計思考流程,並具備講課、教練能力。
- 曾參與台大不一樣思考社設計思考工作坊、東華大學設計思考工作坊、 Stanford x NTU 設計思考工作坊共十幾場。
- 介紹設計思考步驟流程,帶領學員用實際的議題走過設計思考流程。